time4education.com 2011-12-31

# PRIVACY STATEMENT

Triumphant Institute of Management Education Pvt Ltd (T.I.M.E.), the owner of the time4education.com, is committed to protecting your right to privacy and it is our policy to respect the privacy of private communication. The information you provide to us will be held on  T.I.M.E.’s own servers or on third party servers contracted by  T.I.M.E. These may be based in India or abroad. In some cases, information may be stored in a country other than the one you access the site from. The database is stored on servers secured behind a firewall; access to the servers is password-protected and is strictly limited. However, as effective as our security measures are, no security system is impenetrable. We cannot guarantee the security of our database, nor can we guarantee that information you supply will not be intercepted while being transmitted to us over the Internet.

We collect information about our customers in order to help us continually improve the service we offer and so that we can enter into commercial arrangements, including the sale of advertising space.

This Privacy Policy only relates to time4education.com and does not extend to your use of the Internet outside of time4education.com.

We may change our privacy policy from time to time to incorporate necessary future changes. Of course, our use of any information we gather will always be consistent with the policy under which the information was collected, regardless of what the new policy may be.

**What data do we collect?**

We collect personal data which you voluntarily agree to share with us and certify it as being accurate during the registration / enrolment or enquiry process. This data includes (but may not be restricted to):

  * Name (including first and last name)
  * Email address
  * Mobile phone number
  * Postal address
  * Postal code
  * Demographic information (like your age, gender, occupation, professional experience, education, etc.);
  * Preferences and interests (such as newspapers read and so on);
  * Financial information (like account or credit card numbers); and
  * Opinions of features on our websites.

We do not monitor your use of the Internet; neither do we use cookie technology or any other technology to monitor your use of time4education.com.

We may receive and collect certain anonymous information in standard usage logs through our Web server. This information may include the IP address assigned to the computer you use while accessing time4education.com.

We may combine personal information collected from you with other information from data available with us to provide a better overall experience, including customizing content for you in both forms - online (or electronic) as well offline.

If you use a bulletin board or chat room on this site, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums.

We are the sole owners of your information collected by us at several different points on our Website.

**What do we do with the information we collect?**

We may use personal information about you to build up a profile of your performance(s), preferences and to track your progress over the duration of the programme for which you have enrolled with us.

We may use personal information to provide the services you've requested, including services that display customized content and advertising.

We use this information for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this information to contact you.

We may also use personal information for auditing, research and analysis to operate and improve 

T.I.M.E.’s products and services.

We will not sell your personal information to any third party for commercial gains. However, we may, at times, mail promotional material that we believe will be of relevance to you on behalf of third parties and for which we may receive a consideration from the party in question. However, even in such situations, all data will remain solely in the possession of 

T.I.M.E. and will not be shared with any third party.

We may share information with third parties in limited circumstances, including when complying with legal process, preventing fraud or imminent harm, and ensuring the security of our network and services.

We may present information to advertisers who wish to advertise on our website. When we present information to our advertisers it is to help them understand our audience and confirm the value of advertising on our website. Such information is in the form of aggregated statistics on traffic to various pages within our site.

**Your choices**

We offer you choices when we ask for personal information, whenever reasonably possible.

You may decline to provide personal information to us. In such instances the extant of online and offline support that you receive may be limited as a result of this.

We make good faith efforts to provide you access to your personal information upon request and to let you correct such data if it is inaccurate and delete it, when reasonably possible.

For any doubts/clarifications or additional information that you may require,   
please contact us at 

[info@time4education.com](mailto:info@time4education.com)General Terms and ConditionsRefund Policy
